<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<game>
	<title>Horribunnies</title>
	<release-date>TBD</release-date>
	<website>https://horribunnies.com/</website>
	<press-can-request-copy>TRUE</press-can-request-copy>

	<platforms>
		<platform>
			<name>Steam</name>
			<link>http://www.steampowered.com/</link>
		</platform>
	</platforms>

	<prices>
	</prices>

	<description>
	Horribunnies is a bunny-raising game where the player gets to feed, clean and pet their bunnies. However, this care is not misplaced : the player has to carry out orders for customers who want to adopt bunnies. The player can part ways with bunnies matching specific criteria -such as their color or length of their ears- in exchange for resources. As such traits are inherited genetically, the player will selectively encourage the breeding of its bunnies !
	</description>
	<histories></histories>
	<history>
		Lenophie participated in a game-jam organized by Abiding Bridge mid-2019. There, they met Pakrett, a graphic designer, the kind of talent Lenophie had been looking for to bring their vision to life ! Bunny enthusiasts as they are, they both settled for developing a bunny-related game in a minimal amount of time, so they could tell if they liked working together. The scope of the game grew and... voilà, the team expanded with the arrival of a musician, a narrative designer and another graphic designer while the game is now announced to be released on Steam !
	</history>

	<features>
		<feature>Bond with the cutest virtual bunnies you've ever seen, they come in all shapes and sizes but require the same amount of petting !</feature>
		<feature>Send some bunnies for adoption so you can, in return, keep pampering to your favorite bun. :3</feature>
		<feature>Traits are inherited genetically, breed responsibly !</feature>
		<feature>Everything is as flashy and sweet as it can get, from lovely graphics to sugary musics !</feature>
	</features>
	
	<trailers>
	</trailers>
	
	<awards>
	</awards>
	
	<quotes>
	</quotes>
	
	<additionals>
	</additionals>

	<credits>
		<credit>
			<person>Lenophie</person>
			<website>https://twitter.com/Lenophie</website>
			<role>Initiator, Game Designer, Developer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Pakrett</person>
			<website>https://himeija.com</website>
			<role>Artistic Direction, Art</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Eva Vesschemoët</person>
			<website>https://www.linkedin.com/in/eva-vesschemo%C3%ABt-6b6694151/</website>
			<role>Additional Art, Web Design</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Valentin Bilot</person>
			<website>https://twitter.com/vbilot</website>
			<role>Music, Sound Design</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Simon Trucchi</person>
			<role>Narrative Design</role>
		</credit>
	</credits>

	<contacts>
		<contact>
			<name>Inquiries</name>
			<mail>horribunnies@gmail.com</mail>
		</contact>
		<contact>
			<name>Twitter</name>
			<link>https://twitter.com/Horribunnies</link>
		</contact>
		<contact>
			<name>Facebook</name>
			<link>https://facebook.com/Horribunnies</link>
		</contact>
		<contact>
			<name>Instagram</name>
			<link>https://instagram.com/Horribunnies</link>
		</contact>
		<contact>
			<name>Youtube</name>
			<link>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCT6uHcP-1rH3QW7WVEEz6vg</link>
		</contact>
	</contacts>
</game>