<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<game>
	<title>Horribunnies</title>
	<release-date>TBD</release-date>
	<website>https://horribunnies.com/</website>
	<press-can-request-copy>TRUE</press-can-request-copy>

	<platforms>
		<platform>
			<name>Steam</name>
			<link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1187990/Horribunnies</link>
		</platform>
	</platforms>

	<prices>
	</prices>

	<description>
		Horribunnies is a kawaii bunny-raising game... or is it? In Horribunnies, you get to pet, raise and genetically engineer cute bwunnies~~ You will help Pâquerette, the petshop's owner, take the best care of the little creatures while Ophéline, the cynical back-shop manager, will encourage you to treat your bunnies *differently* in order to boost their value. Will your bunny business become the sweetest or the most profitable?
	</description>
	<histories></histories>
	<history>
		Lenophie participated in a game-jam organized by Abiding Bridge mid-2019. There, they met Pakrett, a graphic designer, the kind of talent Lenophie had been looking for to bring their vision to life! Bunny enthusiasts as they are, they both settled for developing a bunny-related game in a minimal amount of time, so they could tell if they liked working together. The scope of the game grew and... voilà, the team expanded with the arrival of a musician, a narrative designer and another graphic designer while the game is now announced to be released on Steam!
	</history>

	<features>
		<feature>Bond with the cutest virtual bunnies you've ever seen, they come in all shapes and sizes but require the same amount of petting!</feature>
		<feature>Send some bunnies for adoption so you can, in return, keep pandering to your favorite one. :3</feature>
		<feature>Get food, equipment and cosmetics for your buns so they can get as happy as bunnily possible!!</feature>
		<feature>Everything is as flashy and sweet as it can get, from lovely graphics to sugary musics!</feature>
		<feature>Traits are inherited genetically, breed responsibly! You don’t want cheap-looking bunnies, do you?</feature>
		<feature>Genetically engineer your bunnies to boost their value: If you figure out how their genes work, you can land a killer bun!</feature>
		<feature>Take an alternative approach: My methods may not be to Pâquerette’s taste, but if you stick with me, we will definitely change this pet shop.</feature>
	</features>
	
	<trailers>
		<trailer>
			<name>Horribunnies' announcement trailer (EN)</name>
			<youtube>-Mf7CyF41fE</youtube>
		</trailer>
		<trailer>
			<name>Horribunnies' announcement trailer (FR)</name>
			<youtube>Nz-MrKGMUcc</youtube>
		</trailer>
		<trailer>
			<name>Ophéline reveal trailer (EN)</name>
			<youtube>sZQ3k4sA4Jo</youtube>
		</trailer>
	</trailers>
	
	<awards>
	</awards>
	
	<quotes>
	</quotes>
	
	<additionals>
		<additional>
			<title>Abiding Bridge</title>
			<description>Abiding Bridge is our publisher. This publisher enables french developers to publish games without creating a company. It's neat and we love them.</description>
			<link>https://abidingbridge.com</link>
		</additional>
	</additionals>

	<credits>
		<credit>
			<person>Lenophie</person>
			<website>https://twitter.com/Lenophie</website>
			<role>Concept, Game Design, Development, Project Management</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Pakrett</person>
			<website>https://himeija.com</website>
			<role>Artistic Direction, Art, Additional Game Design</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Eva Vesschemoët</person>
			<website>https://www.linkedin.com/in/eva-vesschemo%C3%ABt-6b6694151/</website>
			<role>Art, Web Design</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Valentin Bilot</person>
			<website>https://twitter.com/vbilot</website>
			<role>Music, Sound Design</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Célia Vesco</person>
			<website>https://www.linkedin.com/in/c%C3%A9lia-vesco-76674256</website>
			<role>Producer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Simon Trucchi</person>
			<website>https://www.linkedin.com/in/simon-trucchi-4b184647</website>
			<role>Narrative Design</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Julie Rozaire</person>
			<website>https://www.linkedin.com/in/julie-rozaire-2b88a414b/</website>
			<role>Voice Acting, Video Editing</role>
		</credit>
	</credits>

	<contacts>
		<contact>
			<name>Inquiries</name>
			<mail>horribunnies@gmail.com</mail>
		</contact>
		<contact>
			<name>Twitter</name>
			<link>https://twitter.com/Horribunnies</link>
		</contact>
		<contact>
			<name>Facebook</name>
			<link>https://facebook.com/Horribunnies</link>
		</contact>
		<contact>
			<name>Instagram</name>
			<link>https://instagram.com/Horribunnies</link>
		</contact>
		<contact>
			<name>Youtube</name>
			<link>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCT6uHcP-1rH3QW7WVEEz6vg</link>
		</contact>
	</contacts>
</game>